{
    "subject": "resource/Guy_Leverne_Fake",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_military_personnel_of_the_Spanish\u2013American_War",
    "human_readable": "Guy Leverne Fake is the subject of Category:American_military_personnel_of_the_Spanish\u2013American_War.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9644097685813904,
            "question": "During which conflict was Guy Leverne Fake an American military personnel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8777803778648376,
            "question": "What was Guy Leverne Fake's role in the military?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8701239228248596,
            "question": "Who is Guy Leverne Fake?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8531537055969238,
            "question": "Which war did Guy Leverne Fake participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7135195732116699,
            "question": "What nationality was Guy Leverne Fake?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6010128855705261,
            "question": "What is Guy Leverne Fake's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5788271427154541,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the Spanish\u2013American War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5332261323928833,
            "question": "Are there any historical records or documents about Guy Leverne Fake?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5057839751243591,
            "question": "What were the outcomes of the Spanish-American War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48371684551239014,
            "question": "Were there any significant battles in the Spanish-American War?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Guy Leverne Fake is the subject of Category:American_military_personnel_of_the_Spanish\u2013American_War.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the outcomes of the Spanish-American War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records or documents about Guy Leverne Fake?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the Spanish\u2013American War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1364_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents provided contain information about Guy Leverne Fake, including his military service during the Spanish-American War and his subsequent career as a lawyer and judge."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Guy Leverne Fake, including his service in the U.S. Army during the Spanish-American War. This supports the claim that he is a subject of the Category:American_military_personnel_of_the_Spanish\u2013American_War."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}